Finding Aid for Office of the Vice President for Research (University of Michigan), Records, 1950-2001
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Charles G. Overberger, 1950-1982
  - General Files
    - Reference, 1965-1982
      - Labor and Industrial Relations, Institute of
        - 1974-1976 (Box 21)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - Lamont-Hussey Observatory, 1971-1975 (Box 21)
      - Law School, 1973-1978 (Box 21)
      - Library, North Campus, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
      - Library Science, School of, 1974-1978 (Box 21)
      - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
        - 1972-1976 (Box 21)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - L General (Box 21)
      - Mann, Floyd C., 1973 (Box 21)
      - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering, 1976-1978 (Box 21)
      - Mathematics Department, 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - McMath-Hill Observatory, 1973-1976 (Box 21)
      - McMath-Hulbert Observatory, 1974-1979 (Box 21)
      - MECHA (Chicanos), 1974 (Box 21)
      - Mechanical Engineering, Department of, 1973-1978 (Box 21)
      - Medical Care Organization, 1977 (Box 21)
      - Medical Chemistry, 1978 (Box 21)
      - Medical School
        - 1973-1976 (Box 21)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - Medical Science Research Building, 1977-1978 (Box 21)
      - Mental Health Research Institute, 1972-1978 (Box 21)
      - Mental Retardation, Institute for Study of, 1973-1976 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Historical Collections, 1975-1978 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Student Assembly, 1980-1982 (Box 22)
      - Microbiology, Department of, 1975-1978 (Box 22)
      - Music, School of, 1972-1978 (Box 22)
      - M General (Box 22)
      - National Humanities Institute (John Eadie), 1974-1976 (Box 22)
      - National Institute of Health, DNA Consultant, February 1977 (Box 22)
      - National Institute of Health, Research Support Grants, 1973-1975 (Box 22)
      - Natural Resources, School of, 1973-1978 (Box 22)
      - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering
        - General, 1973-1978 (Box 22)
        - Center Feasibility Study, 1977-1979 (Box 22)
      - Near East and North African Studies, Center for, 1975-1978 (Box 22)
      - Near Eastern Studies, Center for, 1975 (Box 22)
      - Neurology, Department of, 1978 (Box 22)
      - Neuroscience Laboratory Building (Box 22)
      - Neurosurgical Head Protection Program, 1976-1978 (Box 22)
      - Northshore UM Club (Glenview, IL), 1977 (Box 22)
      - Noyes Foundation Grant, 1975-1977 (Box 22)
      - Nuclear Engineering, Department of, 1974-1978 (Box 22)
      - Nuclear Medicine, 1978 (Box 22)
      - Nursing School
        - 1973-1976 (Box 22)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 22)
      - Obstetrics and Gynecology, Department of, 1976 (Box 22)
      - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health, Department of, 1973-1978 (Box 22)
      - Ophthalmology, Department of, 1976-1977 (Box 22)
      - Oriental Research, American Schools of, 1978-1979 (Box 22)
      - O General (Box 22)
      - Parks, David G., 1972 (Box 22)
      - Patents
        - Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 22)
        - Development Account, 1974 (Box 22)
        - Miscellaneous Individuals
          - 1974-1976 (Box 22)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 22)
        - Policy
          - 1973-1975 (Box 22)
          - 1975-1976 (Box 22)
          - 1976-1978 (Box 22)
        - Taylor, Harvey M., 1979 (Box 22)
        - Voorhees, John J. (Box 23)
          - 1972-1976 (Box 23)
          - 1977-1978 (Box 23)
      - Payne, Beverly C. (Postgraduate Medicine), 1979 (Box 23)
      - Payroll Department, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
      - Perry Building (Box 23)
      - Personnel Department
        - 1974-1976 (Box 23)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 23)
      - Pharmacology, Department of, 1974-1978 (Box 23)
      - Pharmacy, College of, 1972-1978 (Box 23)
      - Physical Education, Department of, 1976-1978 (Box 23)
      - Physics, Department of
        - 1971-1976 (Box 23)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 23)
        - Computer Committee, 1978 (Box 23)
      - Physiology, Department of, 1974-1978 (Box 23)
      - Plant Extension Committee
        - 1973-1974 (Box 23)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 23)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 23)
      - Polish Academy of Sciences, 1978-1979 (Box 23)
      - Political Science, Department of, 1973-1978 (Box 23)
      - Political Studies, Center for, 1974-1978 (Box 23)
      - Population Planning Department
        - 1975-1976 (Box 23)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 23)
      - Population Studies, Center for, 1974-1978 (Box 23)
      - Posen, Village of (Water Problem), 1978 (Box 23)
      - Positions, Interest in
        - 1973-1975 (Box 23)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 24)
      - Position Emission Tomography (PET), 1978 (Box 24)
      - Post-Doctoral Fellowship Institutional Allowances, 1974 (Box 24)
      - Post-Doctoral Scholars, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
      - President, UM
        - 1972-1976 (Box 24)
        - 1977-1978, 2 folders (Box 24)
      - President's Reports, 1972-1979 (Box 24)
      - Privacy, Rights of and Access to Information, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
      - Professional Organization Membership, 1973-1976 (Box 24)
      - Psychiatry, Department of, 1974-1978 (Box 24)
      - Psychology, Department of
        - 1972-1976 (Box 24)
        - 1976-1978 (Box 24)
      - Public Health, School of
        - 1972-1976 (Box 24)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 24)
        - 1978-1979 (Box 24)
      - Public Policy Studies, Institute of, 1972-1978 (Box 24)
      - Purchasing, 1978 (Box 24)
      - P General (Box 24)
      - Quantimet 720 Image Analysis Facility, 1978-1979 (Box 24)
      - Recommendations (Sought/Made), 1975-1978 (Box 24)
      - Regents
        - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 24)
        - Requests, 1973-1978 (Box 24)
      - Remote Sensing, UM-MSU, Committee on, 1968-1975 (Box 24)
      - Research Advisory Council; Equipment Review Subcommittee, 1972-1975 (Box 24)
      - Research Incentives, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
      - Research Management Improvement, NSF Proposal for, 1972-1975 (Box 24)
      - Research Management Reports
        - 1972 (Box 24)
        - 1977 (Box 24)
      - Research Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 24)
      - Research News, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
      - Research on Learning and Teaching, Center for (Box 24)
      - Research on Social Organization, Center for, 1974-1978 (Box 24)
      - Residential College, 1974-1976 (Box 24)
      - Rickman, Geraldine, Associates Inc. [removed by dept.], 1975-1976 (Box 24)
      - Russian and East European Studies, Center for, 1977 (Box 25)
      - R General, 1975-1978 (Box 25)
      - Saint Joseph Mercy Hospital, N. Ingalls St.
        - General, 1977-1979 (Box 25)
        - Use of Top Three Floors (Zander Committee), 1978-1979 (Box 25)
      - Scholars Press, 1975-1977 (Box 25)
      - Science Research Club, 1978 (Box 25)
      - SCRIPT (Stanford Computerized Information Profile Technique), 1977-1978 (Box 25)
      - Signature Authorization, 1965-1978 (Box 25)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of, 1976 (Box 25)
      - Smith, Allan F., circa 1974 (Box 25)
      - Social Work, School of, 1972-1978 (Box 25)
      - Sociology, Department of, 1972-1978 (Box 25)
      - Sources and Uses of Funds (LeLong's Committee) (Box 25)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for, 1977 (Box 25)
      - Southern Africa, University Committee on, 1979 (Box 25)
      - Space Physics Research Laboratory, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
      - Space Research Building, 1975-1978 (Box 25)
      - Specialized Population Resource Center, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
      - Staff Benefits, Office of, 1979 (Box 25)
      - State Relations and Planning, Vice-President for, 1972-1976 (Box 25)
      - Student
        - Dissertations, 1977 (Box 25)
        - Financial Aid, 1975 (Box 25)
        - Government, 1974 (Box 25)
        - Grievance Procedures, 1977 (Box 25)
        - Minority, 1976 (Box 25)
        - Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box 25)
        - Services, Office of, 1972-1976 (Box 25)
      - Surgery, 1976-1977 (Box 25)
      - Surveys, 1975-1978 (Box 25)
      - S General (Box 25)
      - Telecommunications, 1975-1979 (Box 25)
      - Telephone Operations, 1973-1978 (Box 25)
      - Transportation Certificate Program, 1978 (Box 25)
      - Travel, 1974-1978 (Box 25)
      - Turner Geriatric Clinic, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
      - T General (Box 25)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
      - University Audits, 1972-1978 (Box 25)
      - University Hospital, 1974-1979 (Box 25)
      - University Libraries, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
      - University Record, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
      - University Relations and Development, Vice-President for, 1972-1976 (Box 25)
      - Urban and Regional Planning, 1978 (Box 25)
      - Urban Health Research, Program for, 1978-1980 (Box 25)
      - U General (Box 25)
      - Values and Science, Collegiate Institute for, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
      - Vice-President and Chief Financial Officer, 1972-1976 (Box 25)
      - Visitors, 1976-1978 (Box 25)
      - Water Resources Program, 1972-1978 (Box 25)
      - Western European Studies, Center for, 1976 (Box 25)
      - Willow Run Laboratories (ERIM)
        - General, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
        - Proposals, 1972 (Box 25)
        - Realignment (Box 26)
          - 1969-1971 (Box 26)
          - 1972, 2 folders (Box 26)
      - Wilson, James T., 1972-1980 (Box 26)
      - Women's Research Club, 1978 (Box 26)
      - Women Scientists and Engineers at UM (NSF Report), 1978 (Box 26)
      - W General (Box 26)
      - Zoology, Museum of, 1974-1978 (Box 26)
    - Research Support/Interest, 1961-1980
      - B General (Box 26)
      - Battelle Development Corporation, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
      - Burroughs Corporation, 1977 (Box 26)
      - C General (Box 26)
      - D General (Box 26)
      - Dreyfus Teacher-Scholar Grants, 1973-1977 (Box 26)
      - E General (Box 26)
      - Eastern Michigan University, 1972 (Box 26)
      - Ecology Research Associates, 1974-1977 (Box 26)
      - Electric Power Research Institute, 1973-1976 (Box 26)
      - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan (ERIM), 1972-1977 (Box 26)
      - F General (Box 26)
      - Federal Agencies, Offices and Projects
        - Agriculture, Department of, 1978 (Box 26)
        - Anti-Inflation Measures, 1978 (Box 26)
        - Army, Department of, 1977 (Box 26)
        - Biomedical Research Support Grant Program, 1976-1977 (Box 26)
        - Board of International Food and Agricultural Development (BIFAD) and Title XII, 1978 (Box 26)
        - Central Intelligence Agency, 1976-1979 (Box 26)
        - Commerce, Department of, 1977 (Box 26)
        - Congressional Delegation, 1972-1978 (Box 26)
        - Consumer Products Safety Commission, 1974 (Box 26)
        - Copyrights, 1974 (Box 26)
        - Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency (DARPA), 1978 (Box 26)
        - Defense, Department of, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
        - Energy, Department of, 1977-1978 (Box 26)
        - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 26)
        - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-1976 (Box 26)
        - Freedom of Information Act, 1977 (Box 26)
        - General Accounting Office, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
        - Management and Budget, Office of, Circular A-21, 1970 (Box 26)
        - Maritime Administration, 1975 (Box 26)
        - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
        - National Institute of Education, 1974-1976 (Box 26)
        - National Institute of Health, 1972-1976 (Box 26)
        - National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health, 1975-1977 (Box 27)
        - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1973-1975 (Box 27)
        - National Science Board and National Council on Humanity, 1973-1976 (Box 27)
        - National Science Foundation
          - General
            - 1972-1977 (Box 27)
            - 1978 (Box 27)
          - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
        - Naval Academy, 1977 (Box 27)
        - Nuclear Regulatory Commission
          - 1975-1977 (Box 27)
          - 1978 (Box 27)
        - Proxmire, William Senator, Golden Fleece Award, 1979 (Box 27)
        - Science and Technology Committee, US House of Representatives, 1974-1977 (Box 27)
        - Technological Assessment Advisory Councils, Office of Technology Assessment, 1972-1977 (Box 27)
      - Federation of American Scientists, 1975 (Box 27)
      - Ford Foundation, 1972-1977 (Box 27)
      - Foundation for International Technical Corporation (Box 27)
      - G General (Box 27)
      - Holotron Corporation-Battelle Development Corp.
        - 1975-1976 (Box 27)
        - 1977-1980 (Box 27)
      - I General (Box 27)
      - International Association for Great Lakes Research, 1975 (Box 27)
      - International Business Machines, 1972-1977 (Box 27)
      - International Development Center, 1976-1977 (Box 27)
      - International Science and Technology Institute, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 27)
      - Institute for Administrative Advancement, 1976 (Box 27)
      - J General (Box 27)
      - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1970-1973 (Box 27)
      - M General, 1974-1977 (Box 27)
      - Michigan Cancer Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box 27)
      - Michigan Industry: Research and Development Awards, 1978 (Box 27)
      - Michigan Inter-University Cardiovascular Center proposal, 1974 (Box 27)
      - Michigan Inter-University Research Storage Facility proposal, 1974 (Box 27)
      - Michigan Research Foundation, 1961-1974 (Box 27)
      - Michigan, State of
        - Economic Action Council, 1972-1976 (Box 27)
        - Governor's Commission on Higher Education, 1970-1976 (Box 27)
        - Governor's Science and Technology Conference
          - 1976-1977 (Box 27)
          - 1978-1979 (Box 27)
        - Legislature, 1972-1977 (Box 27)
        - Management and Budget, Department of, 1974 (Box 27)
        - Statewide Cost Allocation Plan, 1972-1975 (Box 27)
      - Michigan State University, 1973-1977 (Box 28)
      - Midwest Regional Water Pollution Research Laboratory, 1963-1973 (Box 28)
      - N General (Box 28)
      - O General (Box 28)
      - P General (Box 28)
      - Rand Corporation, 1975 (Box 28)
      - Research Corporation, 1970-1978 (Box 28)
      - Research Facilities and Equipment Needs, 1979 (Box 28)
      - Research Figures, Other Universities, 1976-1978 (Box 28)
      - Rockefeller University, 1973 (Box 28)
      - Stanford University Planning Council for Computer Networking, 1975-1977 (Box 28)
      - T General (Box 28)
      - United Nations Fund for Population Activities, 1977 (Box 28)
      - United Nations University-proposed, 1974 (Box 28)
      - University of Washington, 1973 (Box 28)
      - W General (Box 28)
      - Wayne County General Hospital, 1976 (Box 28)
      - X-Z General (Box 28)
    - Budget, 1973/74-1976/77
      - 1973-1974
        - General Funds, Fiscal, 1974 (Box 28)
        - Budget Base (Preparation Based on 1.2% Reduction), Fiscal, 1974 (Box 28)
        - Radiation Control Services (Box 28)
        - Philological Research (Middle English Dictionary) (Box 28)
        - Laboratory Animal Medicine (Box 28)
        - Institute for Environmental Quality (Box 28)
        - Institute for Social Research (Box 28)
        - Office of Vice-President for Research (Box 28)
        - Neurosciences Laboratory (Box 28)
        - Cancer Research (Box 28)
        - Michigan Memorial (Phoenix Project) (Box 28)
        - Division of Research Development and Administration (Box 28)
        - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 28)
        - Research Maintenance (Box 28)
        - 1.3 Savings Reduction, Fiscal, 1973; 1974 (Box 28)
      - 1974-1975
        - Budget Reductions (1%, General Fund Units), Fiscal, 1975 (Box 28)
        - Office of Research Administration (Box 28)
        - Institute for Environmental Quality (Box 28)
        - Office of Vice-President for Research (Box 28)
        - Statistical Research Laboratory (Box 28)
        - Laboratory Animal Care Unit (Box 28)
        - Computing Center (Box 28)
        - Institute for Social Research (Box 28)
        - Sea Grant (Box 28)
        - Cancer Research (Box 28)
        - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 28)
        - Highway Safety Research Institute (Box 28)
        - Neurosciences Laboratory (Box 28)
        - Philological Research (Middle English Dictionary) (Box 28)
        - Radiation Control Services (Box 28)
        - Michigan Memorial (Phoenix Project) (Box 28)
      - 1975-1976
        - General Fund Allocations (Box 28)
        - Cancer Research (Box 28)
        - Radiation Control (Box 28)
        - Computing Center (Box 28)
        - Philological Research (Box 28)
        - Michigan Memorial (Phoenix Project) (Box 28)
        - Sea Grant Program (Box 28)
        - Neurosciences Laboratory (Box 28)
        - Laboratory Animal Medicine Unit (Box 28)
        - Institute for Environmental Quality (Box 28)
        - Institute for Social Research (Box 28)
        - Statistical Research Laboratory (Box 28)
        - Division of Research Development and Administration (Box 28)
        - Vice-President for Research (Box 28)
        - Macromolecular Research Center (Box 28)
        - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 28)
        - Budget Reductions (Box 29)
          - Tentative 1-1/2-3% General Fund Units), Fiscal, 1976 (Box 29)
          - Merit Computing Center (Box 29)
          - General Fund Budget
            - 1% Reduction of Fiscal allocation, 1976 (Box 29)
            - Proposed Increases (Box 29)
            - Summary Reductions (Box 29)
          - Hiring Freeze, Fiscal, 1976 (Box 29)
      - 1976-1977
        - General Fund Allocations (Box 29)
        - Special Moratorium on Accounts per Letter (Box 29)
        - General Fund Budget
          - Preparation of Provisional 95% and 97% Budgets (Box 29)
          - Budget Reduction Criteria Requested by Vice-President Rhodes (Box 29)
          - Meeting with Budget Priorities Committee (Box 29)
          - Preparation of Adjusted Base (after reductions) (Box 29)
        - Computing Center (Box 29)
        - Radiation Control Service (Box 29)
        - Unit for Laboratory Alumni Medicine (Box 29)
        - Institute for Environmental Quality (Box 29)
        - Office of Vice-President for Research (Box 29)
        - Neuroscience Laboratory (Box 29)
        - Cancer Research (Box 29)
        - ICPR (Box 29)
        - Summer Institute in Survey Research (Box 29)
        - Division of Research Development (Box 29)
        - Nuclear Reactor (Box 29)
        - Philological Research (Box 29)
        - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 29)
        - Institute for Social Research (Box 29)
  - Report File (Units Reporting to VP), 1950-1982
    - Biophysics Research Division (Institute of Science and Technology)
      - 1972-1976 (Box 29)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 29)
    - Computing Center
      - 1972-1976 (Box 29)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 29)
    - Computing Center Expansion (Capital Outlay Requests), 1974-1976 (Box 29)
    - Computing Center's Users Group (Steering Committee), 1973 (Box 29)
    - Computer Policy and Utilization, University Committee on
      - 1972-1974 (Box 29)
      - 1975 (Box 30)
      - 1976-1977, 4 folders (Box 30)
      - 1978-1979 (Box 30)
      - Study Group, 1978 (Box 30)
      - Survey, Phases I-III (Box 30)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 47)
      - Review
        - 1977 (Box 47)
        - 1978 (Box 47)
        - 1979 (Box 47)
    - Computer Purchase Review, 1972-1976 (Box 30)
    - Dental Research Institute
      - General
        - 1972-1977 (Box 30)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 31)
      - Meeting with NIH (Dr. Scott et al.), 1976 (Box 31)
      - Policy Committee
        - 1972-1976 (Box 31)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 31)
      - Search Committee, 1975 (Box 31)
      - Site Visit
        - July 23, 1975 (Box 31)
        - May 12-14, 1976 (Box 31)
    - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA)
      - General
        - 1972-1975 (Box 31)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 31)
        - 1976 (Box 31)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 31)
      - Keeley, J.J. (Box 31)
      - Policy Committee/Site Visit, October 1978 (Box 31)
      - Recharge Rates, 1971-1974 (Box 31)
      - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1973-1978 (Box 31)
      - Site Visit, October 1977 (Box 32)
      - Staff Meetings, 1975-1977 (Box 32)
    - Energy Research
      - Committee on, 1976-1977 (Box 32)
      - Office of
        - General
          - 1976 (Box 32)
          - 1977 (Box 32)
          - 1978 (Box 32)
        - Advisory Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
    - Environmental Quality, Institute for (continued in Box 45)
      - General
        - 1970-1976 (Box 32)
        - 1977-1982 (Box 32)
      - Advisory Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 32)
      - Norman, A.G., 1972-1982 (Box 32)
      - Noyes Foundation Grant, 1977-1978 (Box 32)
      - Policy Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 32)
      - Fellows and Fellowships
        - Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation, 1974-1976
          - Active (alphabetically by name of fellow), 12 folders (Box 45)
          - Inactive, 2 folders (Box 45)
        - Rockefeller Foundation, 1972-1975; 22 folders (Box 45)
        - Rockefeller Foundation, 1972-1975; 10 folders (Box 46)
      - Rockefeller Foundation
        - Policy Statement, 1974 (Box 46)
        - Reports
          - 1970, 2 folders (Box 46)
          - 1971, 2 folders (Box 46)
          - 1972, 2 folders (Box 46)
          - 1974 (Box 46)
          - 1976, 2 folders (Box 46)
        - Statement of Account, 6 folders (Box 46)
        - Miscellanea, 2 folders (Box 46)
      - Jessie Smith Noyes
        - General (Box 46)
        - Self-Evaluation Reports
          - 1975 (Box 46)
          - 1976 (Box 46)
      - Environmental Studies, Institute for (University of Wisconsin) (Box 46)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center
      - General
        - 1974-1976 (Box 32)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 32)
      - Advisory Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 32)
      - External Advisory Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 32)
      - Environmental Data and Information Center, 1976-1977 (Box 32)
      - Research Vessels (Box 33)
        - 1972-1976 (Box 33)
        - Laurentian, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
    - Great Lakes Research Division
      - General
        - 1972-1976 (Box 33)
        - 1978-1980 (Box 33)
      - Search Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 33)
    - Health Services Research Center
      - General, 1976-1981 (Box 33)
      - Policy Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 33)
      - Proposal
        - Volume 1; Preparation, 1972 (Box 33)
        - Volume 2; Preparation, 1973-1975 (Box 33)
        - Volume 3; Proposal and Award, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
        - Volume 4; Correspondence, 1976 (Box 33)
    - Highway Safety Research Institute
      - General
        - 1973-1975 (Box 33)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 33)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 33)
      - Advisory Council, 1972-1976 (Box 33)
      - Baboons, Use of in Crash Tests, 1978 (Box 33)
      - Cadavers, Use of in Crash Tests, 1980 (Box 33)
      - Carroll, Philip S., 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 34)
      - General
        - 1972-1976 (Box 34)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 34)
      - Industrial Development Division
        - 1973-1976 (Box 34)
        - 1977-1978 (Box 34)
      - Review Committee, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Institute for Social Research
      - Correspondence (General)
        - 1972-1974 (Box 34)
        - 1975-1976 (Box 34)
        - 1977-1979 (Box 34)
      - Building Addition, 1974-1975 (Box 34)
      - Finance Reports and Memos
        - 1972-1975 (Box 34)
        - 1975-1978 (Box 34)
      - Inter-University Consortium for Political and Social Research, 1975-1978 (Box 34)
      - Research Utilization of Scientific Knowledge, Center for (CRUSK), 1978 (Box 34)
    - Laboratory Animal Medicine, Unit for
      - General
        - 1972-1973 (Box 34)
        - 1974 (Box 34)
        - 1975 (Box 34)
        - 1976 (Box 34)
        - 1977 (Box 34)